<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Project on</title><link>https://electricblocks.github.io/docs/project/</link><description>Recent content in Project on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2021 19:12:30 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://electricblocks.github.io/docs/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Overview</title><link>https://electricblocks.github.io/docs/project/overview/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2021 19:19:09 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://electricblocks.github.io/docs/project/overview/</guid><description>Problem Definition Our project is defined by several problems. The core issue is to develop software that allows users to model electrical power flow. The software must model power flow realistically enough to enable quality education and research. Additionally, the software must work in a virtual video game environment and must be easy to use.
Background Minecraft is a 3D/VR video game that enables the creation of complex virtual worlds. The block based nature of the game makes it very easy for players to build nearly any structure.</description></item><item><title>Design</title><link>https://electricblocks.github.io/docs/project/design/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 13:28:23 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://electricblocks.github.io/docs/project/design/</guid><description>Our design process began in early September of 2020 and was focused entirely on solving our problem definition. Most of our overall design decisions were finalized by the end of September, but we continued to tweak the design as new discoveries were made.
Initial Design In the initial documentation provided to us, our client outlined several suggestions on how to approach this project. They suggested the using Minecraft or Minetest as the platform for hosting our software.</description></item><item><title>Documentation</title><link>https://electricblocks.github.io/docs/project/documentation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 13:29:09 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://electricblocks.github.io/docs/project/documentation/</guid><description>Problem Definition Original Project Description Product Requirements Project Management Project Schedule Design Validation Plan Presentations Snapshot #1 Snapshot #2 (Poster - Large File) Concept Design Review Engineering Release Review</description></item></channel></rss>