<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Electric Blocks on</title><link>https://electricblocks.github.io/docs/electric-blocks/</link><description>Recent content in Electric Blocks on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2021 20:41:52 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://electricblocks.github.io/docs/electric-blocks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About Electric Blocks</title><link>https://electricblocks.github.io/docs/electric-blocks/about-eb/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2021 20:45:16 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://electricblocks.github.io/docs/electric-blocks/about-eb/</guid><description>Electric Blocks is the Minecraft client/server mod that functions as the interface for EBPP. This mod adds all the necessary blocks, tile entities, GUIs, etc. needed for power flow simulations. In multiplayer, this mod must be installed on both the client and server to work properly. In single-player, only installing the mod on the client is necessary.</description></item><item><title>Singleplayer Installation</title><link>https://electricblocks.github.io/docs/electric-blocks/singleplayer-installation/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 17:32:56 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://electricblocks.github.io/docs/electric-blocks/singleplayer-installation/</guid><description>So you want to use Electric Blocks, but you don&amp;rsquo;t have any IT admins running a server for you? Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, Electric Blocks works just fine in singleplayer.
⚠️ Running Electric Blocks and EBPP on the same computer will increase the workload on it. We recommend that you use a reasonably modern computer when using the Electric Blocks mod and EBPP at the same time. If this is not an option, check with your educational institution to see if they can setup a multiplayer server or public EBPP instance.</description></item><item><title>Usage</title><link>https://electricblocks.github.io/docs/electric-blocks/usage/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 17:27:44 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://electricblocks.github.io/docs/electric-blocks/usage/</guid><description>This guide assumes you already have a working Electric Blocks mod installation. If not, please go back to the installation guides.
Blocks and Items Unlike other items in Minecraft, Electric Blocks cannot be crafted using in-game materials (yet). The only way to obtain these blocks is through the creative menu or commands. We recommend that you use creative mode. When you&amp;rsquo;re in creative mode, press E on your keyboard to open up the block selection menu (this may vary if you have alternative keybindings or control schemes).</description></item></channel></rss>