<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Prologue on</title><link>https://electricblocks.github.io/docs/prologue/</link><description>Recent content in Prologue on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://electricblocks.github.io/docs/prologue/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introduction</title><link>https://electricblocks.github.io/docs/prologue/introduction/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://electricblocks.github.io/docs/prologue/introduction/</guid><description>More specifically, Electric Blocks is a Minecraft Forge mod that allows you to run realistic power flow simulations for educational and engineering purposes. This site contains documentation for using this mod.
This mod is sponsored by the University of Idaho as part of the Capstone Design project.</description></item><item><title>Quick Start</title><link>https://electricblocks.github.io/docs/prologue/quick-start/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 13:59:39 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://electricblocks.github.io/docs/prologue/quick-start/</guid><description>Normal Installation 💡 This guide only applies if you're connecting to a mulitplayer server hosted by someone else. For single player or multiplayer setup, please review the entire installation guide. 1. Install Minecraft Minecraft Java Edition is required to use this mod. If you have Minecraft installed you can skip this step.
Otherwise go to the minecraft website and download and install it: https://www.minecraft.net/download
After downloading the client, double-click the icon to run it.</description></item><item><title>Help</title><link>https://electricblocks.github.io/docs/prologue/help/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 18:08:06 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://electricblocks.github.io/docs/prologue/help/</guid><description>We know that there is a lot of documentation for this mod so this help page should answer some common questions and give some general information.
FAQ What&amp;rsquo;s this mod for? Why would I use it? Electric Blocks is a Minecraft mod designed to aid in power engineering research and instruction. This mod simplifies the process of constructing an electrical network and running a power flow study on it. If you don&amp;rsquo;t know what that means, this mod might not be for you.</description></item></channel></rss>